justintimberlake.com 2012-12-31

# Justin Timberlake | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

### Tennman Digital Privacy Policy

Tennman Digital LLC and its affiliated companies (collectively, “Tennman Digital”) has created this privacy statement (“Privacy Policy”) to explain and summarize how we collect, use and protect, or in some cases do not protect, your personal information as you interact with us online through the website (the “Website”). Tennman Digital reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new privacy statement at this location. Therefore, you are responsible for periodically checking the Privacy Policy for changes. Your use of the Website is governed at all times by the Tennman Digital Terms of Service. If you are visiting from outside the United States there may be special rules or limitations on your use of this Website.

### 1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Tennman Digital collects and uses information you provide to us or that we learn from your use of this Website. Tennman Digital does not share your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We may share your personal information where it is necessary for us to complete a transaction or do something that you have asked us to do. Whenever we may need to share your personal information, we try to provide you with the information you need to make informed choices.

Tennman Digital collects and uses personal information from you in several ways:

  * **User Accounts**  In order to access certain areas of the Website or certain Services, you may be required to create a user account and provide certain personal information such as your name, your email address, your birth date, your user ID, your password, and other personal information. If you would like to subscribe to additional Services, you may be required to provide additional information such as your telephone number, your mobile service provider, and your address. We may use the information you provide in online registration forms to notify you periodically about important changes to the Website or the Services (such as a change to this Privacy Policy or notice of a security breach), new products and services, and special offers and contests that may be of interest to you. Regardless of any other provision of this Privacy Policy, we may permanently store any personal information provided by you via such registration process.

  * **For contests conducted on the Website** , we use the personal information you provide only for the purpose of contacting you if you win a prize and sending the prize to you. We do not use the contact information contained in contest entries to create mailing lists or for any other purpose, unless you have simultaneously subscribed to a mailing list or consented to such other use. For further information about how we handle entries to a particular contest, please consult the contest rules. All contests held on this site are limited to persons above a certain age. Accordingly, we will ask each contestant to provide year of birth, as well as name, address, and email address. Please refer to the specific age requirements for each contest as rules may vary from contest to contest.

  * **Where you provide optional information** , such as information about your interests and hobbies, Tennman Digital uses this information on an aggregate basis to enable us to better understand our users, develop new products, and improve our products and services. Tennman Digital may also use this information to update you about new promotions, albums, or products, or to send you newsletters and other communications and materials relating to Tennman Digital, the Website, or the Services. This direct marketing will only come from Tennman Digital — we will not allow affiliates to do any direct marketing. Where practical, Tennman Digital limits the access of our business partners and service providers who assist with technical support and customer service through the use of confidentiality provisions and agreements that are intended to enforce this Privacy Policy.

  * **Website Usage**  Tennman Digital, or Tennman Digital business partners or authorized service providers, may observe your activities, preferences, and transactional data (such as your IP address and browser type) relating to your use of this Website. While we may collect or log this information, we generally do not identify you or match this information with your other personal information. We may use this collected or logged information to diagnose website technical problems, to facilitate your use of the site, or to track aggregate traffic patterns throughout the Website.

  * **Online Transactions**  If we offer you the opportunity to purchase products online and you choose to purchase such products, you may be asked to share personal information in addition to the information provided to create a user account, such as credit card information, in order to complete a transaction. In addition, you may be asked for information needed to complete your order, contact you to confirm the order, and provide related customer service. This information is used, for example, to effect your transactions, to create and share aggregate reports about these transactions, and to perform credit fraud screening services for transactions between you and Tennman Digital and/or our authorized service providers. We may also use your information as permitted by law to perform credit checks, or to report or collect debts owed.

  * **Recruitment and Job Applications**  You may provide us with personal information, such as that contained on a resume or a curriculum vitae, in connection with a job application or inquiry. We may use this information throughout Tennman Digital for the purpose of employment consideration or your inquiry. We may keep your information on file for a reasonable period of time for future consideration.

  * **Cookies and Web Beacons**  A cookie is a piece of data stored on Your computer tied to Your information. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once You close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on Your hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. We use cookies to store information about Your user account. By setting a cookie on the Website, You would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on the Website. If You reject the cookie, You may still use the Website. The only drawback to this is that You may be limited in some areas of the Website. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on the Website. Some of our business partners use cookies on the Website (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. We also use “web beacons” (also known as “1×1 gifs”) to monitor your activities around the Website.

  * **Public and Shared Areas**  Any information and other Content (as defined in the Tennman Digital Terms of Service) disclosed in public areas of the Website will become public information. We cannot control the use of information or other Content disclosed in public forums, such as bulletin boards, news groups, communication facilities and chat rooms. You should exercise caution when disclosing information in these public areas and should refrain from disclosing your personal information in such areas. Please remember that any information or other Content that is disclosed in these areas, including your name, becomes available to others and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.  _TENNMAN DIGITAL WILL TREAT ANY MESSAGE BOARD POSTINGS, FEEDBACK, EMAILS OR SUGGESTIONS YOU PROVIDE TO US AS NON-CONFIDENTIAL AND NON-PROPRIETARY. IF YOU CHOOSE TO USE YOUR REAL NAME, YOUR NAME WILL BE AVAILABLE TO AND VIEWABLE BY ANYONE USING THE WORLD WIDE WEB AND/OR USING A SEARCH ENGINE._

### 2\. ADDITIONAL USES OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

Certain Third Party Transactions. Tennman Digital may work with its business partners and authorized service providers to provide technical and customer support, shipping, credit card processing, product fulfillment or other services. Where practical, Tennman Digital shall require these parties to safeguard personal information you provide to us. To the extent it is necessary for these parties to complete their contractual obligations to Tennman Digital, these third parties may collect, have access to or process your personal information. Tennman Digital endeavors to limit their use of your personal information to the purpose for which it was shared. Tennman Digital may sometimes permit our business partners and authorized service providers to have access to aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information. In some circumstances, our business partners or service providers may be the only party who stores your personal information.

  * **Mergers, Acquisitions and Bankruptcy**  If Tennman Digital should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another company, or if Tennman Digital should decide to buy, sell or reorganize some part or all of its business, Tennman Digital may disclose your personal information to prospective or actual purchasers or receive personal information from sellers. It is Tennman Digital’s practice to seek appropriate protection for personally identifiable information disclosed or received in these types of transactions.

  * **As Required by Law and Other Extraordinary Disclosures**  Tennman Digital may be required to disclose your personal information if it: (a) believes it is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process (such as a court order, subpoena, search warrant, etc.) or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; (b) would potentially mitigate our liability in an actual or potential lawsuit; (c) is otherwise necessary to protect our rights or property; or (d) is necessary protect the interest of other users of our Website.

  * **Additional Third Party Sharing**  Tennman Digital may share aggregated user information with third parties such as Sony Interscope or Sony Music Entertainment, and their respective affiliated companies. These third parties may use this information to better reach their targeted audiences.

### 3\. CHILDREN

Tennman Digital does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, you should not attempt to register for the Website or Services or send information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. If a child under 13 submits information through any part of the Website without verification of parental consent, and we learn the person submitting the information is a child or such consent has not been verified, we will attempt to delete this information as soon as possible. Because we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13, we do not use or disclose such information to third parties. If you believe that Tennman Digital may have any information about a child under 13, please contact us at  _360 Ritch Street, 3rd Floor, San Francisco, CA 94107_.

### 4\. SECURITY

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. We use reasonable security measures to protect data transmissions. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such measures. Tennman Digital is not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of your information or Content posted by you may remain viewable in cashed or archived pages or if other users who you permitted to access your information have copied or stored your information.

If Tennman Digital learns of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using this Website or providing personal information to us, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of the Website. Tennman Digital may post a notice on our Website if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to view the Website. In these circumstances, Tennman Digital may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us at  _360 Ritch Street, 3rd Floor, San Francisco, CA 94107_.

### 5\. INTERNATIONAL VISITORS AND CUSTOMERS

Because Tennman Digital operates globally, circumstances could arise where it is necessary for us to make your personal information available to our worldwide business units. Privacy laws differ across the globe. If it is necessary for the purposes for which you have shared personal information with us for us to share your information within Tennman Digital&apos;s global operations, we will do so consistent with this Privacy Policy and you agree to such transfers.

This Website is hosted in the United States. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from United States law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States and by providing your personal data you consent to that transfer. When you provide personal data to Tennman Digital or our service providers or vendors, you consent to the processing of your data in the United States as the Website is operated in the United States. Parts of this Privacy Policy may not apply to visitors from outside the United States because certain services are not offered to those outside the United States.

### 6\. LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITES AND CO-BRANDED WEBSITES

This Website may contain links to third-party sites, however, please be aware that Tennman Digital is not responsible for and cannot control the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies for these other sites, as they may differ from ours. TENNMAN DIGITAL HAS NOT REVIEWED ALL OF THESE THIRD PARTY SITES AND DOES NOT CONTROL NOR IS TENNMAN DIGITAL RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY OF THESE SITES, THEIR CONTENT OR THEIR PRIVACY POLICIES. TENNMAN DIGITAL DOES NOT ENDORSE OR MAKE REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THEM, OR ANY INFORMATION, PRODUCTS OR MATERIALS FOUND THERE, OR ANY RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM USING THEM. IF YOU DECIDE TO ACCESS ANY OF THE THIRD PARTY SITES LINKED FROM THE WEBSITE, YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN RISK.

This Website may contain links to co-branded web sites that may display Tennman Digital’s logo and trademarks, or the names or images of artists included in the Website, but which are maintained by third parties. Please read the privacy policy on the co-branded site for the applicable privacy practices relating to personal information collected via that site, as it may differ from this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies solely to personal information collected by Tennman Digital.

Advertisements that appear on the Website are sometimes delivered (or “served”) directly to users by third party advertisers. Such third parties automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and “web beacons” (also known as “1×1 gifs”) to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. Tennman Digital does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on the Website unless you choose to share it with them.

This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies and other tracking technologies by Tennman Digital and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

### 7\. CONTACT PREFERENCES

When you provide Tennman Digital with personal information, you agree that we may communicate with you by email or otherwise, including to send marketing communications from us or from third parties. For marketing communications, we generally try to communicate by the method and on topics of your choosing. Generally, when we contact you, we will try to provide you with an easy and convenient way to notify us if you would not like further similar communications.

### 8\. CONTACTING TENNMAN DIGITAL

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, or would like to make changes to your personal information or contact preferences, or delete personal information you have provided to us, please email us at [support@tennmandigital.com](mailto:support@tennmandigital.com). You may make changes to your personal information or contact preferences through the Website after you login using your username and password.

#### Postal Mail Address:

_Tennman Digital LLC  
360 Ritch St., 3rd Floor  
San Francisco, CA 94107_

If you have a privacy concern regarding Tennman Digital or this Privacy Policy and if you cannot satisfactorily resolve it through the use of this Website you should then write to: 360 Ritch Street, 3rd Floor, San Francisco, CA 94107. In the event that we are still unable to resolve your concerns Tennman Digital is committed to cooperating to achieve a proper resolution of your privacy concerns.

**Effective Date: May 8, 2009**
